Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records UA146
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine class schedules and committee minutes, 1968 -- 2009; UA146.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  - 1st Year Spring, 1984; UA146.003.036.00053 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C,D, E, 1984 -- 1985; UA146.003.036.00054 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1978; UA146.003.036.00055 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Untis C, D, E, 1976; UA146.003.036.00056 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year Renal Systems M'81, 1978; UA146.003.036.00057 (Box 36)
  - 1st year Spring, 1978; UA146.003.036.00058 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Untis A & B, 1976; UA146.003.036.00059 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Spring, 1976; UA146.003.036.00060 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1984; UA146.003.036.00061 (Box 36)
  - Course Schedules, 1973 -- 1974; UA146.003.036.00062 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year Systems- Musculoskeletal M'82, 1980; UA146.003.036.00063 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year Systems- Reproduction/Human Sexuality M'82, 1982; UA146.003.036.00064 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C, D, E, 1981; UA146.003.036.00065 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1981; UA146.003.036.00066 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1978; UA146.003.036.00067 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Year- Units C, D, E, 1979; UA146.003.036.00068 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Fall, 1975; UA146.003.036.00069 (Box 36)
  - 1st Year Spring, 1977; UA146.003.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Dermatology, 1979; UA146.003.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Pharmacology, 1979; UA146.003.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year- Psychiatry, 1978 -- 1979; UA146.003.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Physical Diagnosis, 1979; UA146.003.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Systems Pulmonary, 1979; UA146.003.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Course Schedules, 1979 -- 1980; UA146.003.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Class of 1983 First Year Third Trimester, UA146.003.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Units A & B, 1980; UA146.003.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Class of 1983 Second Year, UA146.003.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Systems Reproductive and Human Sexuality, 1979; UA146.003.037.00011 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Musculoskeletal, 1979; UA146.003.037.00012 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Systems Cardiovascular M'82, 1979; UA146.003.037.00013 (Box 37)
  - GI Systems M'81, 1979; UA146.003.037.00014 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year Systems Endocrine, 1979; UA146.003.037.00015 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1977; UA146.003.037.00016 (Box 37)
  - 2nd Year- Units A & B, 1975; UA146.003.037.00017 (Box 37)
  - Curriculum Committee/Course Evaluations, 2003 -- 2005; UA146.003.037.00018 (Box 37)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2003 -- 2004; UA146.003.037.00019 (Box 37)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2005; UA146.003.037.00020 (Box 37)
  - Second Year- Fall Sem, 1993; UA146.003.037.00021 (Box 37)
  - Class of 1992 Second Year Fall Semester, 1989; UA146.003.037.00022 (Box 37)
  - Second Year Spring Semester, 1995; UA146.003.037.00023 (Box 37)
  - Class of 1997 Second Year Spring Semester, 1995; UA146.003.037.00024 (Box 37)
  - First Year Fall Semester, 1993; UA146.003.037.00025 (Box 37)
  - TUMS Evaluation System, 1996; UA146.003.037.00026 (Box 37)
  - Audience Response Systems, 2004; UA146.003.037.00027 (Box 37)
  - Ethics Meeting, 2009; UA146.003.037.00028 (Box 37)
  - Course Schedules, 1997 -- 2001; UA146.003.037.00029 (Box 37)
  - Course Schedules, 1991 -- 1995; UA146.003.037.00030 (Box 37)
  - First Year Spring Semester, 1992 -- 1993; UA146.003.037.00031 (Box 37)
  - First Year Fall 2002, UA146.003.037.00032 (Box 37)
  - Emails/Schedules, 2002; UA146.003.037.00033 (Box 37)
  - Emails/Schedules, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.003.037.00034 (Box 37)
  - First Year Spring 2003, UA146.003.037.00035 (Box 37)
  - Brown OSCE, 2006; UA146.003.037.00036 (Box 37)
  - Second Year Spring, 2003; UA146.003.037.00037 (Box 37)
  - Second Year Fall 2002, UA146.003.037.00038 (Box 37)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1998 -- 2006; UA146.003.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Phase I, 1999; UA146.003.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Phase II, 1999; UA146.003.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Phase III, 1999; UA146.003.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1984 -- 1998; UA146.003.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Core Collaborators, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.003.038.00006 (Box 38)
  - Core Collaborators, 1996; UA146.003.038.00007 (Box 38)
  - System Committees, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.003.038.00008 (Box 38)
  - Immune System- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00009 (Box 38)
  - Endocrine, 1997; UA146.003.038.00010 (Box 38)
  - Reproductive- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00011 (Box 38)
  - Gastrointestinal- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00012 (Box 38)
  - Pulmonary- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00013 (Box 38)
  - Musculoskeletal- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00014 (Box 38)
  - Cardiovascular- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00015 (Box 38)
  - Renal- Cell, Tissue, Organ, 1997; UA146.003.038.00016 (Box 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.003.038.00017 (Box 38)
  - System Committee Members, 1997; UA146.003.038.00018 (Box 38)
  - Pharmacology Curriculum Proposals, 1992; UA146.003.038.00019 (Box 38)
  - CC Background Info, 1968; UA146.003.038.00020 (Box 38)
  - Section Coordinators and Class Schedules, 1991 -- 2001; UA146.003.038.00021 (Box 38)
  - CTOB Ethics, 2003 -- 2004; UA146.003.038.00022 (Box 38)
  - THCI Online Learning, 2003; UA146.003.038.00023 (Box 38)
  - 2nd Year Academic Schedule, 2002; UA146.003.038.00024 (Box 38)
  - 2nd Year, 2002; UA146.003.038.00025 (Box 38)
  - Fall 2001-2002 Changes, UA146.003.038.00026 (Box 38)
  - Second year Academic Schedule, 2001; UA146.003.038.00027 (Box 38)
  - 1st Year, 2002; UA146.003.038.00028 (Box 38)
  - 1st year, 2001; UA146.003.038.00029 (Box 38)
  - 2nd Year, 2001; UA146.003.038.00030 (Box 38)
  - Surveys AAMC Related, 1999; UA146.003.038.00031 (Box 38)
  - Fall Schedule Hours, 1999 -- 2000; UA146.003.038.00032 (Box 38)
  - Spring Schedule, 1992; UA146.003.038.00033 (Box 38)
  - Class Schedules, 1993 -- 1996; UA146.003.038.00034 (Box 38)
  - CC Minutes, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.003.038.00035 (Box 38)
  - CC Minutes, 1998 -- 1999; UA146.003.038.00036 (Box 38)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 1998 -- 1999; UA146.003.038.00037 (Box 38)
  - CC Minutes, 1997 -- 1998; UA146.003.038.00038 (Box 38)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 1997 -- 1998; UA146.003.038.00039 (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Attachments, 1997 -- 1999; UA146.003.038.00040 (Box 38)
  - Phase I, II, and III Report, 1994; UA146.003.038.00041 (Box 38)
  - Blue Sky Report, 1968; UA146.003.038.00042 (Box 38)
  - 1983 Report, UA146.003.038.00043 (Box 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997 -- 1998; UA146.003.038.00044 (Box 38)
  - M Y Lee Report, 1994; UA146.003.038.00045 (Box 38)
  - Cardiovascular System Committee, 1995; UA146.003.038.00046 (Box 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.038.00047 (Box 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Survey to Assess Dr. Grannum Sant's Phase II Recommendations, 1996; UA146.003.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - PBL Subcommittee Report, 1995; UA146.003.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Maine "MedStart" Report, 1995; UA146.003.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - PDS Report, 1995; UA146.003.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Retreat, 1994; UA146.003.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Exam Subcommittee, 1995; UA146.003.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee Evaluation Project, 1996; UA146.003.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Class Schedules, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.003.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - First Year Class Schedules, 1988 -- 1997; UA146.003.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - Second Year Class Schedules, 1991 -- 1998; UA146.003.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - Phase I and Phase II Subcommittees, 1993; UA146.003.039.00012 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1993 -- 1994; UA146.003.039.00013 (Box 39)
  - Committee Information, 1992 -- 1993; UA146.003.039.00014 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1990 -- 1991; UA146.003.039.00015 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1988 -- 1990; UA146.003.039.00016 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1993; UA146.003.039.00017 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00018 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00019 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00020 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00021 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00022 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00023 (Box 39)
  - Computer Survey, 1997; UA146.003.039.00024 (Box 39)
  - Grape Distributions, 1994 -- 1999; UA146.003.039.00025 (Box 39)
  - Ambulatory, 1995; UA146.003.039.00026 (Box 39)
  - Cardiovascular Meeting, 1995; UA146.003.039.00027 (Box 39)
  - Evaluation Subcommittee, 1995; UA146.003.039.00028 (Box 39)
  - Examination Subcommittee, 1997; UA146.003.039.00029 (Box 39)
  - Genetics, 1995; UA146.003.039.00030 (Box 39)
  - PBL Subcommittee, 1995; UA146.003.039.00031 (Box 39)
  - PCP Clerkship, 1997; UA146.003.039.00032 (Box 39)
  - Vertical Integration, 1993; UA146.003.039.00033 (Box 39)
  - Report-Clinical Curriculum Planning Committee, 1987; UA146.003.039.00034 (Box 39)
  - Cibu Geigy Award, 1995; UA146.003.039.00035 (Box 39)
  - Primary Care Pilot, 1995; UA146.003.039.00036 (Box 39)
  - Board Review, 1997; UA146.003.039.00037 (Box 39)
  - CC Minutes, 2002 -- 2003; UA146.003.039.00038 (Box 39)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 2002 -- 2003; UA146.003.039.00039 (Box 39)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 2002; UA146.003.039.00040 (Box 39)
  - CC Minutes, 2000 -- 2001; UA146.003.039.00041 (Box 39)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 2000 -- 2001; UA146.003.039.00042 (Box 39)
  - CC Minutes, 1999 -- 2000; UA146.003.039.00043 (Box 39)
  - CC Attendance Sheets, 1999 -- 2000; UA146.003.039.00044 (Box 39)
  - Agenda, 1996; UA146.003.039.00045 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00046 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00047 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00048 (Box 39)
  - Meeting Notes, 1996; UA146.003.039.00049 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1995; UA146.003.039.00050 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00051 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00052 (Box 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.039.00053 (Box 39)
  - Office of Educational Affairs Presentation, UA146.003.042.00011 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.042.00012 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997; UA146.003.042.00013 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996; UA146.003.042.00014 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Attendants/Labels Curriculum Committee, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.003.042.00015 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Phase 1, 1993; UA146.003.042.00016 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - RWJ, 1994; UA146.003.042.00017 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
    Robert Wood Johnson Foundation
  - 1992, UA146.003.042.00018 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Phase 2, 1992; UA146.003.042.00019 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
  - Phase 3, 1994; UA146.003.042.00020 (Box UA146 Shared 1)
- Mary Y. Lee's files, 1968 -- 2007; UA146.004; 8.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject files from Mary Y Lee.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Exhibit Sharewood, 1999; UA146.004.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - Teaching Portfolio, 1994 -- 1995; UA146.004.029.00002 (Box 29)
  - Faculty Promotion, appointment, and handbook, 1995 -- 1998; UA146.004.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Vision statement, 1996; UA146.004.029.00004 (Box 29)
  - AMSA, 1994 -- 1999; UA146.004.029.00005 (Box 29)
  - Alumni, 1997 -- 2000; UA146.004.029.00006 (Box 29)
  - Faculty, 1992 -- 1995; UA146.004.029.00007 (Box 29)
  - Comp. task force, 1982 -- 1994; UA146.004.029.00008 (Box 29)
  - Domestic violence, 1992 -- 1994; UA146.004.029.00009 (Box 29)
  - Minutes and agenda, 1992 -- 1994; UA146.004.029.00010 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum background information, 1986 -- 1993; UA146.004.029.00011 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum correspondence, 1993 -- 1994; UA146.004.029.00012 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum membership, 1993; UA146.004.029.00013 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum working groups, 1993; UA146.004.029.00014 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum phase committee summaries, 1993; UA146.004.029.00015 (Box 29)
  - Task force on curriculum historical documents, 1983; UA146.004.029.00016 (Box 29)
  - Grant proposal, 1996 -- 2000; UA146.004.029.00017 (Box 29)
  - UME-21 and Shering Plough Primary CareScholars Program, 1995 -- 1998; UA146.004.029.00018 (Box 29)
  - PEW committee, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.004.029.00019 (Box 29)
  - USDA grant, 2000; UA146.004.029.00020 (Box 29)
  - Pew Proposal, 1995 -- 1997; UA146.004.029.00021 (Box 29)
  - HSR Postdoc fellow/ Harry Selker, 1997 -- 2000; UA146.004.029.00022 (Box 29)
  - FIPSE final proposal, 2000 -- 2002; UA146.004.029.00023 (Box 29)
  - National Science Foundation an integrated multimedia curriculum, UA146.004.029.00024 (Box 29)
  - Nutrition grant, 1998; UA146.004.029.00025 (Box 29)
  - Grant application, 1995; UA146.004.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - IAMS, 1993; UA146.004.030.00002 (Box 30)
  - Grants, 1994 -- 2000; UA146.004.030.00003 (Box 30)
  - Grants, 1994 -- 2000; UA146.004.030.00004 (Box 30)
  - CEMMP Kathyrn Lasch, 1996 -- 2000; UA146.004.030.00005 (Box 30)
  - White and Yelon documents, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.004.030.00006 (Box 30)
  - Family medicine, 1999 -- 2001; UA146.004.030.00007 (Box 30)
  - Fourth year eval form, 1990 -- 2000; UA146.004.030.00008 (Box 30)
  - Department of Emergency Medicine student manual 1-4th year student clerkship curriculum, 1994 -- 1997; UA146.004.030.00009 (Box 30)
  - Third year clerkships checklist, orientation, and prep, 1997 -- 1998; UA146.004.030.00010 (Box 30)
  - Physcian Diagnosis Updates, 1999; UA146.004.030.00011 (Box 30)
  - Physcian Diagnos Course, 1974 -- 1997; UA146.004.030.00012 (Box 30)
  - Violence prevention for children and youth, 1997; UA146.004.030.00013 (Box 30)
  - Alternative medicine, 1995 -- 1997; UA146.004.030.00014 (Box 30)
  - Master Clinician Series M'99, 1996; UA146.004.030.00015 (Box 30)
  - Principlals and Practices (PPM) and Physician Diagnosis (PD), 1995 -- 1997; UA146.004.030.00016 (Box 30)
  - General Internal Medicine Generalist Education Leadership Development Project (GIMGEL), 1999 -- 2001; UA146.004.030.00017 (Box 30)
  - Genetics in primary care training curriculum manual, 2001; UA146.004.030.00018 (Box 30)
  - Genetics in primary care, 1999 -- 2001; UA146.004.030.00019 (Box 30)
  - Curriculum retreat, 1993 -- 1994; UA146.004.030.00020 (Box 30)
  - Bingham program, 1992 -- 1998; UA146.004.030.00021 (Box 30)
  - Mini-CEX and patient log, 1998 -- 1999; UA146.004.030.00022 (Box 30)
  - Dermatology curriculum, 1993; UA146.004.030.00023 (Box 30)
  - Medicine clerkship, 1993 -- 1997; UA146.004.030.00024 (Box 30)
  - Overview of Medicine Clerkship, 1987; UA146.004.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - OB/GYN Clerkship, 1997; UA146.004.031.00002 (Box 31)
  - Opthamology Curriculum, 1993; UA146.004.031.00003 (Box 31)
  - Neurology, 1997; UA146.004.031.00004 (Box 31)
  - Pediatric Clerkship, 1997; UA146.004.031.00005 (Box 31)
  - Physical/Medicine Rhab, 1994; UA146.004.031.00006 (Box 31)
  - Psychiatry, 1999; UA146.004.031.00007 (Box 31)
  - Surgery Clerkship, 1997; UA146.004.031.00008 (Box 31)
  - Urology, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.004.031.00009 (Box 31)
  - Residency Match, 2002; UA146.004.031.00010 (Box 31)
  - Policies, Assorted Files, 1995; UA146.004.031.00011 (Box 31)
  - TISC Task Force, 1997; UA146.004.031.00012 (Box 31)
  - Practical Consulting, 1997; UA146.004.031.00013 (Box 31)
  - HHMI/HRSA, 2002; UA146.004.031.00014 (Box 31)
  - HSDB, 2001; UA146.004.031.00015 (Box 31)
  - Related Articles, 1993; UA146.004.031.00016 (Box 31)
  - Genetics (GPC), 2000; UA146.004.031.00017 (Box 31)
  - Genetics in Primary Care, 2000; UA146.004.031.00018 (Box 31)
  - AAMC Info, 2001; UA146.004.031.00019 (Box 31)
  - AMA, 2000; UA146.004.031.00020 (Box 31)
  - New Course Committee, 1998; UA146.004.031.00021 (Box 31)
  - Clinical Education Task Force, 2001; UA146.004.031.00022 (Box 31)
  - Teaching Portfolios, 1997 -- 1999; UA146.004.031.00023 (Box 31)
  - The Educator's Portfolio, 1998; UA146.004.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Board of Overseers, 1993 -- 1995; UA146.004.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - Chinatown Charter School, 1995; UA146.004.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Community Service (Chinatown), 1996; UA146.004.032.00004 (Box 32)
  - Multimedia Resource Center MRC Advisory Board, 1997; UA146.004.032.00005 (Box 32)
  - Primary Care, 1997; UA146.004.032.00006 (Box 32)
  - Special Programs, 2001 -- 2003; UA146.004.032.00007 (Box 32)
  - Ongoing Projects, 1991 -- 1992; UA146.004.032.00008 (Box 32)
  - Evaluations, 2000; UA146.004.032.00009 (Box 32)
  - Medical Programs, 1997 -- 2001; UA146.004.032.00010 (Box 32)
  - External Review, 1994; UA146.004.032.00011 (Box 32)
  - Diversity Workshop, 1994; UA146.004.032.00012 (Box 32)
  - EMMC, 1997 -- 1999; UA146.004.032.00013 (Box 32)
  - Student Info, 2001 -- 2004; UA146.004.032.00014 (Box 32)
  - Genetics in Primary Care, 2000; UA146.004.032.00015 (Box 32)
  - Evaluation Project, 1996; UA146.004.032.00016 (Box 32)
  - Fall Semester M07 Student Directory, 2007; UA146.004.032.00017 (Box 32)
  - Fourth Year, 1997; UA146.004.032.00018 (Box 32)
  - Cirriculum Planning Committee, 1998; UA146.004.032.00019 (Box 32)
  - CBS, 1998; UA146.004.032.00020 (Box 32)
  - Patterns of Learning, 2000; UA146.004.032.00021 (Box 32)
  - Best Teachers, 1999; UA146.004.032.00022 (Box 32)
  - Reviews/Evaluations, 1996; UA146.004.032.00023 (Box 32)
  - Evaluations, 1996; UA146.004.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - HSOB, 2003; UA146.004.032.00025 (Box 32)
  - USMLA Handouts, 2001 -- 2003; UA146.004.032.00026 (Box 32)
  - NBME, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.004.032.00027 (Box 32)
  - Board Review, 1996 -- 2000; UA146.004.033.00001 (Box 33)
    US Medical Licensing Examination
  - Blue Sky Report, 1968; UA146.004.033.00002 (Box 33)
    Tufts Medicine Curricula Reform
  - Brown Blueprint, 1993; UA146.004.033.00003 (Box 33)
    Brown University Educational Blueprint for School of Medicine
  - Brown Checklist, 1995; UA146.004.033.00004 (Box 33)
    Brown University Physical Exam Checklist
  - Peer Review, 2000; UA146.004.033.00005 (Box 33)
    Temple University Handbook for Peer Review
  - Needlestick Policy, 1998; UA146.004.033.00006 (Box 33)
  - Disabilities, 2002; UA146.004.033.00007 (Box 33)
    Tufts Resources and References
  - MD/MBA Program, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.004.033.00008 (Box 33)
  - MD/MPH Program, 1995 -- 1996; UA146.004.033.00009 (Box 33)
  - MD/MS/BS Program, UA146.004.033.00010 (Box 33)
    Folder Empty
  - MD/MA Program, 1997; UA146.004.033.00011 (Box 33)
  - Report 1996 (of the Information Technology Taskforce), UA146.004.033.00012 (Box 33)
  - ITEB, 1998; UA146.004.033.00013 (Box 33)
    Information Technology Executive Board
  - Policy and Planning Meeting, 1997; UA146.004.033.00014 (Box 33)
  - Executive Council, 1998; UA146.004.033.00015 (Box 33)
  - Multimedia Teaching Committee, 1998; UA146.004.033.00016 (Box 33)
  - Genetics in Primary Care (GPC), 2000; UA146.004.033.00017 (Box 33)
  - Being Well, 1997; UA146.004.033.00018; The Society for Professional Well-Being (Box 33)
    Newsletter
  - NEMC: International Health Care and Telemedicine, 1997; UA146.004.033.00019 (Box 33)
    New England Medical Center
  - Managed Care at a Glance, 1997; UA146.004.033.00020 (Box 33)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute, 1995 -- 2000; UA146.004.033.00021 (Box 33)
    Includes publication "Impact"
  - Proposal to the Pew Charitable Trusts, 1996; UA146.004.033.00022; Tufts Managed Care Institute (Box 33)
  - TMCI Policy and Planning Meeting, 1997; UA146.004.033.00023 (Box 33)
    Tufts Managed Care Institute
  - Family Medicine Clerkship, 1995 -- 1997; UA146.004.033.00024 (Box 33)
  - Lawrence Family Practice, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.004.033.00025 (Box 33)
  - Library/HSDB, UA146.004.033.00026 (Box 33)
  - MSPREP, 2002 -- 2003; UA146.004.033.00027 (Box 33)
    Master of Science in Pain Research and Education Program
  - OGDP/Graduate Progs., 2003; UA146.004.033.00028 (Box 33)
    Office of Graduate Degree Programs
  - Security Working Group, 2002; UA146.004.033.00029 (Box 33)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1993 -- 1996; UA146.004.033.00030 (Box 33)
    Core Collaborators Group
  - Dept. of Medicine Retreat, 1995; UA146.004.033.00031 (Box 33)
  - Guidelines for Preparation of Protocols for Submittal to the Human Investigation Review Committee, 1999; UA146.004.033.00032 (Box 33)
    Tufts Health Sciences and New England Medical Center
  - Compassionate Care (Schwartz Foundation), UA146.004.033.00033 (Box 33)
  - Visit to Peking University with President and Mrs. DiBiaggio, 1996; UA146.004.033.00034 (Box 33)
    Memo
  - Hypnosis Course, 1997; UA146.004.033.00035 (Box 33)
  - Curriculum Survey [1 of 2], UA146.004.033.00036 (Box 33)
  - Curriculum Survey [2 of 2], UA146.004.033.00037 (Box 33)
    Includes Surgery Clerkship Student Evaluation Report 2000-2001
  - AAMC Medical School Graduation Questionnaire, 1996 -- 1998; UA146.004.033.00038 (Box 33)
    Association of American Medical Colleges
  - Preparing Residents to Succeed in Managed Care: Teaching Tools for Faculty [Binder 1], 1999; UA146.004.033.00039; Tufts Managed Care Institute (Box 33)
  - Preparing Residents to Succeed in Managed Care: Teaching Tools for Faculty [Binder 2] [1 of 3], 1999; UA146.004.033.00040; Tufts Managed Care Institute (Box 33)
  - Preparing Residents to Succeed in Managed Care: Teaching Tools for Faculty [Binder 2] [2 of 3], 1999; UA146.004.033.00041 (Box 33)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Chairman's Retreat: Presented by Tufts Managed Care Institute, 1996; UA146.004.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Managed Care at a Glance: Common Terms, 1995; UA146.004.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - Integrating Managed Care Principles and Perspectives into Medical Education, 1996; UA146.004.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Health Care Institute: Curriculum Guide on Managing Care: A Systems-Based Approach Version 1.1, 2002; UA146.004.034.00004 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute Board Meeting, 1997; UA146.004.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute Symposium: Preparing Residents to Succeed in Managed Care, 1997; UA146.004.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute: Preparing Residents to Succeed in Managed Care: Curriculum Development Workbook, 1997; UA146.004.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Health Care Institute: Making Care Decisions at the End of Life, 2003; UA146.004.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute: Managed Care Curriculum Retreat, 1999; UA146.004.034.00009 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute: On-line Advisory Committee, 1999; UA146.004.034.00010 (Box 34)
  - Basics of Decision Analysis [1 of 2], 1993; UA146.004.034.00011 (Box 34)
    Society for Medical Decision-Making
  - Basics of Decision Analysis [2 of 2], 1993; UA146.004.034.00012 (Box 34)
  - Computer Literacy and Clinical Decision Making, 1987; UA146.004.034.00013 (Box 34)
  - TISC Task Force Meeting, 1997; UA146.004.034.00014 (Box 34)
    Tufts Information Superhighway Committee
  - PBL Case Writing Workshop, 1996; UA146.004.034.00015 (Box 34)
    Problem-Based Learning
  - PBL Case Writing Retreat, 1996; UA146.004.034.00016 (Box 34)
  - PBL Case Writing Retreat for 3rd Year Internal Medicine Curriculum, 1996; UA146.004.034.00017 (Box 34)
  - Objectives Workshop, 1996; UA146.004.034.00018 (Box 34)
  - PBL Case Writing Retreat Tufts Managed Care Institute, 1996 -- 1998; UA146.004.034.00019 (Box 34)
  - TISC Task Force Final Report, 1997; UA146.004.034.00020 (Box 34)
  - Robert Wood Johnson, 1993; UA146.004.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - Portfolio Workshop, 1997; UA146.004.035.00002 (Box 35)
  - Portfolio Workshop, 1997; UA146.004.035.00003 (Box 35)
  - Family Medicine Clerkship Facilitator's Manual, 2000; UA146.004.035.00004 (Box 35)
  - Committee on Redefining Criteria for Clinical Appointments and Promotions, 1999; UA146.004.035.00005 (Box 35)
    Folder 1 of 2
  - Committee on Redefining Criteria for Clinical Appointments and Promotions, 1999; UA146.004.035.00006 (Box 35)
    Folder 2 of 2